<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<floater
 positioning="centered"
 legacy_header_height="18"
 height="600"
 layout="topleft"
 name="floater_about"
 help_topic="floater_about"
 save_rect="true"
 title="About [APP_NAME]"
 width="515">
  
  <tab_container
    follows="all" 
    top="20"
    left="7"
    height="572" 
    width="501" 
    name="about_tab"
    tab_position="top">
    <panel
      border="true" 
      label="Info"
      help_topic="about_support_tab"
      name="support_panel">
      <text
        follows="top|left|right"
        font="SansSerif"
        height="30"
        layout="topleft"
        left="11"
        name="support_intro"
        top="16"
        width="434"
        wrap="true">
For the latest information about Firestorm, visit 
https://www.firestormviewer.org
      </text>
      <text_editor
        parse_urls="true"
        follows="top|left"
        font="SansSerif"
        height="468"
        bg_readonly_color="Transparent"
        left="5"
        max_length="65536"
        name="support_editor"
        top_pad="5"
        width="489"
        word_wrap="true" />
      <button
        follows="left|top" 
        label="Copy to Clipboard"
        name="copy_btn"
        left="5"
        top_pad="5"
        height="25"
        width="180" />
    </panel>
    <panel
      border="true"
      label="Linden Lab Credits"
      help_topic="about_credits_tab"
      name="credits_panel">
      <text
        follows="top|left|right"
        height="70"
        layout="topleft"
        left="4"
        name="linden_intro"
        top="16"
        width="489"
        wrap="true">
Firestorm would not be possible without the decision from Linden Lab to make their Second Life viewer source code available.

Second Life is brought to you by the Lindens, 
with open source contributions from:
      </text>
      <text_editor
       enabled="false"
       follows="top|left"
       height="458"
       bg_readonly_color="Transparent"
       text_color="LtGray"
       max_length="65536"
       name="contrib_names"
       top_pad="5"
       width="476"
       word_wrap="true">
Dummy Name replaced at run time
      </text_editor>
    </panel>
    <panel
      height="910"
      border="true"
      label="Firestorm Credits"
      help_topic="about_fscredits_tab"
      name="fs_credits_panel">
        <scroll_container
         follows="all"
         layout="topleft"
         left="0"
         name="fs_credits_scroll_container"
         reserve_scroll_corner="false"
         top="16"
         bottom="-1"
         right="-4">
            <panel
             name="fs_credits_scroll_container_content_panel"
             follows="left|top"
             layout="topleft"
             min_height="300"
             top="0"
             background_visible="false"
             left="0"
             right="-15"
             bottom="-1">
                <text
                 follows="top|left|right"
                 height="102"
                 layout="topleft"
                 left="5"
                 name="firestorm_intro"
                 top="0"
                 width="450"
                 wrap="true">
Firestorm is a community development project to improve the SecondLife(tm) Viewer experience. We package contributions from various community developers along with code from Linden Lab and ourselves to bring you a quality, feature-rich viewer experience backed up by a large volunteer support team. Firestorm is brought to you by The Phoenix Firestorm Project, Inc., a non-profit organization.

The Firestorm Development Team:
                </text>
                <text
                 enabled="false"
                 follows="top|left"
                 height="70"
                 bg_readonly_color="Transparent"
                 left="5"
                 text_color="LtGray"
                 max_length="65536"
                 name="firestorm_names"
                 top_pad="4"
                 width="450"
                 wrap="true">
Ansariel Hiller, ArminWeatherHax, Arrehn Oberlander, Beq Janus, Cinder Roxley, Holy Gavenkrantz, Jessica Lyon, Kadah Coba, Kitty Barnett, Liny Odell, LordGregGreg Back, Mobius Ryba, Nicky Dasmijn, PanteraPolnocy, ScentualLust, Selo Jacobus, Tankmaster Finesmith, Techwolf Lupindo, Tonya Souther, Tozh Taurog, Vortex Saito, WoLf Loonie, Wolfspirit Magic, Yay N' Stuff (mygoditsfullofstars), and Zi Ree.
                </text>
                <text
                 follows="top|left"
                 height="15"
                 layout="topleft"
                 left="5"
                 name="fs_contrib_intro"
                 top_pad="8"
                 width="450"
                 wrap="true">
Additional code generously contributed to Firestorm by:
                </text>
                <text
                 enabled="false"
                 follows="top|left"
                 height="215"
                 bg_readonly_color="Transparent"
                 left="5"
                 text_color="LtGray"
                 max_length="65536"
                 name="fs_contrib_names"
                 top_pad="4"
                 width="450"
                 wrap="true">
Albatroz Hird, Alexie Birman, Andromeda Rage, Angeldark Raymaker, Angus Boyd, Animats, Armin Weatherwax, Casper Warden, Chalice Yao, Chaser Zaks, Chorazin Allen, Cron Stardust, Damian Zhaoying, Dan Threebeards, Dawa Gurbux, Denver Maksim, Dragonborn Forzane, Drake Arconis, Felyza Wishbringer, f0rbidden, Fractured Crystal, Geenz Spad, Gibson Firehawk, Hitomi Tiponi, humbletim, Inusaito Sayori, Jean Severine, Katharine Berry, Kittin Ninetails, Kool Koolhoven, Lance Corrimal, Lassie, Latif Khalifa, Laurent Bechir, Magne Metaverse LLC, Magus Freston, Makidoll, Manami Hokkigai, MartinRJ Fayray, McCabe Maxstead, Melancholy Lemon, Melysmile, Mimika Oh, Mister Acacia, MorganMegan, Morgan Pennent, Mysty Saunders, Nagi Michinaga, Name Short, nhede Core, NiranV Dean, Nogardrevlis Lectar, Oren Hurvitz, paperwork, Penny Patton, Peyton Menges, programmtest, Qwerty Venom, Rebecca Ashbourne, Revolution Smythe, Romka Swallowtail, Sahkolihaa Contepomi, sal Kaligawa, Samm Florian, Satomi Ahn, Sei Lisa, Sempervirens Oddfellow, Shin Wasp, Shyotl Kuhr, Sione Lomu, Skills Hak, StarlightShining, Sunset Faulkes, Tapple Gao, Testicular Slingshot, Thickbrick Sleaford, Ubit Umarov, Vaalith Jinn, Vincent Sylvester, Whirly Fizzle, Xenhat Liamano, 小滢 Zi Ying, Zwagoth Klaar and others.
                </text>
                <text
                 follows="top|left"
                 height="35"
                 layout="topleft"
                 left="5"
                 name="fs_support_intro"
                 top_pad="8"
                 width="450"
                 wrap="true">
Special thanks to our Firestorm Support Team, Beta Testers, wiki editors, educators and translators:
                </text>
                <text
                 enabled="false"
                 follows="top|left"
                 height="275"
                 bg_readonly_color="Transparent"
                 left="5"
                 text_color="LtGray"
                 max_length="65536"
                 name="fs_trans_names"
                 top_pad="4"
                 width="450"
                 word_wrap="true">
Afrika Burton, Albatroz Hird, Alexru Resident, alison Seesaw, AnaLucia Loon, Angell Airy, Annuccia Resident, Annuccia Vuckovic, Anubi Alter, Atthosz Amiot, Ayelin Ethaniel, Basement Desade, Bia Scribe, Bluezy Bleac, Clarke2, Christy Mansbridge, Chymy India, Cordoba Cluny, Damian Zhaoying, DARK Mirabella, Emmanuella Checchinato, Ed Merryman, Enigma Conundrum, Eressea Karsin, Erick Gregan, F0RBIDDEN, Fabry String, Fetish3d, Flandria Connolly, Foksy, FreeSpirit Simmering, Gee McAuley, Greatfox Snowpaw, Gweneth Lange, Hatake Kohime, Hiroshi Kumaki, Hope Dreier, Jodi Nikolaidis, JogiTE Clip, Kool Koolhoven, Kosmox Voom, Lachrimo Skytower, Lalwende Leakey, Landaree Levee, Lassie, Lette Ponnier, Lina Pussycat, Lyn Mimistrobell, Marianne Qunhua, Marybeth Oceanlane, Mel Hinarada, Mickeala Praga, Miller Thor, Miro Collas, Mister Acacia, Morgause Whiteberry, Mysty Saunders, Nano Bouscario, narcisssia McMahon, Natem Andel, Nicoletta Schnute, Nisa Maverick, NogarDrevlis Lectar, Norton Burns, PanteraPolnocy, Peewee Musytari, Pisano Smit, PixelProphet Lane, Pol Xaron, Poledra Behemoth, Programmtest, Rander Teskat, Ricky Munz, Riku Highfield, RINOBIT Footman, Robert0 Siamendes, Roth Grut, Sabah Back, SaHaRa Connor, Selene Gregoire, Selo Jacobus, silvanaf Demina, Sniper Siemans, Spartaco Zemenis, Spino Forcella, Srilania Svoboda, Sunset Faulkes, Tanja Levenque, TankMaster Finesmith, Tarlyn Dagger, Thea Brianna, Toy Wylie, Whirly Fizzle, Willow Wilder, Wolfspirit Magic and XLR8RRICK Hudson.
                </text>
                <text
                 follows="top|left"
                 height="78"
                 layout="topleft"
                 left="5"
                 name="fs_art_intro"
                 top_pad="8"
                 width="450"
                 wrap="true">
Firestorm includes Starlight, modified for Firestorm. It is provided by residents for residents, with the intention of providing an alternative, brighter, and hopefully easier to use interface. For further details see &lt;nolink&gt;https://wiki.secondlife.com/wiki/Viewer_Skins/Starlight&lt;/nolink&gt;.

UI Artists and Designers:
                </text>
                <text
                 enabled="false"
                 follows="top|left"
                 height="85"
                 bg_readonly_color="Transparent"
                 left="5"
                 text_color="LtGray"
                 max_length="65536"
                 name="fs_artists_names"
                 top_pad="4"
                 width="450"
                 wrap="true">
Adam Frisby, Alexandrea Fride, DarkAgent Baphomet, David Rowe, Digital Scribe, Dragonborn Forzane, Hitomi Tiponi, Hugh Helendale, KirstenLee Cinquetti, Mobius Ryba, Nadin, Naomah Beaumont, psi Merlin, samm florian, Sammie Benoir, Tommi Waydelich and Vincent Nacon.
                </text>
            </panel>
        </scroll_container>
    </panel>
    <panel
      border="true"
      label="Licenses"
      help_topic="about_licenses_tab"
      name="licenses_panel">
      <text_editor
       enabled="false"
       follows="left|top"
       height="532"
       bg_readonly_color="Transparent"
       left="4"
       text_color="LtGray"
       max_length="65536"
       name="licenses_editor"
       top="16"
       width="474"
       word_wrap="true">
3Dconnexion SDK Copyright (C) 1992-2009 3Dconnexion
APR Copyright (C) 2011 The Apache Software Foundation
Collada DOM Copyright 2006 Sony Computer Entertainment Inc.
cURL Copyright (C) 1996-2010, Daniel Stenberg, (daniel@haxx.se)
DBus/dbus-glib Copyright (C) 2002, 2003 CodeFactory AB / Copyright (C) 2003, 2004 Red Hat, Inc.
expat Copyright (C) 1998, 1999, 2000 Thai Open Source Software Center Ltd.
FMOD Sound System, Copyright (C) Firelight Technologies Pty, Ltd., 1994-2020
FreeType Copyright (C) 1996-2002, 2006 David Turner, Robert Wilhelm, and Werner Lemberg.
GL Copyright (C) 1999-2004 Brian Paul.
GLOD Copyright (C) 2003-04 Jonathan Cohen, Nat Duca, Chris Niski, Johns Hopkins University and David Luebke, Brenden Schubert, University of Virginia.
Havok.com(TM) Copyright (C) 1999-2001, Telekinesys Research Limited.
HACD Copyright (C) 2011, Khaled Mamou (kmamou@gmail.com)
jpeg2000 Copyright (C) 2001, David Taubman, The University of New South Wales (UNSW)
jpeglib Copyright (C) 1991-1998, Thomas G. Lane.
meshoptimizer Copyright (c) 2016-2021 Arseny Kapoulkine
ogg/vorbis Copyright (C) 2002, Xiphophorus
OpenSSL Copyright (C) 1998-2008 The OpenSSL Project.
PCRE Copyright (c) 1997-2012 University of Cambridge
SDL Copyright (C) 1997, 1998, 1999, 2000, 2001, 2002 Sam Lantinga
SSLeay Copyright (C) 1995-1998 Eric Young (eay@cryptsoft.com)
xxHash Copyright (C) 2012-2020 Yann Collet.
zlib Copyright (C) 1995-2012 Jean-loup Gailly and Mark Adler.
Some icons by Joseph Wain / glyphish.com

Second Life Viewer uses Havok (TM) Physics. (c)Copyright 1999-2010 Havok.com Inc. (and its Licensors). All Rights Reserved. See www.havok.com for details.

This software contains source code provided by NVIDIA Corporation.

All rights reserved. See licenses.txt for details.

Voice chat Audio coding: Polycom(R) Siren14(TM) (ITU-T Rec. G.722.1 Annex C)
      </text_editor>
      </panel>
    </tab_container>
</floater>
